<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CAPITOL LAW PARTNERS’s Blog</title><description>Capitol Law Partners - Law Firm providing legal services in the practice areas of Corporate, Commercial, Real Estate, Intellectual Property, and Litigation.</description><link>https://capitollawpartners.com</link><item><title>Green Card - Vize Başvurum Reddedildi Ne Yapmalıyım?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/green-card-vize-basvurum-reddedildi-ne-yapmaliyim</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/green-card-vize-basvurum-reddedildi-ne-yapmaliyim</guid><description> ABD vizesinin reddedilmesi, göçmenlik yolculuğunuzun sonu anlamına gelmez. Başvurunuz reddedildikten sonra atmanız gereken adımları ve Washington, D.C. ve Chicago&apos;daki Capitol Law Partners&apos;ın deneyimli avukatlarının, daha güçlü bir dava için yeniden başvuru veya itiraz sürecinde size nasıl rehberlik edebileceğini öğrenin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ailemi Amerikaya Nasıl Getirebilirim?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/ailemi-amerikaya-nasil-getirebilirim</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/ailemi-amerikaya-nasil-getirebilirim</guid><description>ABD göçmenlik sürecinde en önemli unsurlar, doğru formları hazırlamak, eksiksiz bilgi sağlamak ve süreci zamanında başlatmaktır. Correct Forms, müşterilerine bu üç temel alanda profesyonel destek sağlayarak başvuruların hatasız bir şekilde ilerlemesini garanti eder. Eksik veya hatalı belgelerden kaynaklanan uzun bekleme sürelerini en aza indirerek, müşterilerinin Amerika&apos;da yeni bir hayat kurma yolculuğunu güvenilir, hızlı ve stressiz hale getirir. </description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amerika Birleşik Devletleri&apos;nde Yeşil Kart Almanın Yolları </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/amerika-birlesik-devletlerinde-yesil-kart-almanin-yollari</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/amerika-birlesik-devletlerinde-yesil-kart-almanin-yollari</guid><description> Yeşil Kart almak için birçok yol vardır: aile sponsorluğu (ebeveynler, kardeşler, nişanlı/eş), istihdam temelli vizeler (EB kategorileri), Çeşitlilik Vizesi Çekilişi ve diğer özel programlar. Capitol Law Partners, müşterilerin en uygun yolu seçmelerine yardımcı olur ve kalıcı oturma izni almaları için hukuki destek sağlar. </description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green Card Başvurusu Nasıl Yapılır?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/green-card-basvurusu-nasil-yapilir</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/green-card-basvurusu-nasil-yapilir</guid><description>Green Card olarak bilinen DV-2027 (Diversity Visa) için başvuru süreci için adım adım rehber. Her yıl düzenlenen bu çekilişe yapacağınız başvuru süreci DV-2027 (Green Card) hakkında bilinmesi gerekenleri ele alacağız. </description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apply for a US Visa As a Healthcare Professionals</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-healthcare-professionals-can-work-in-the-u-s</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-healthcare-professionals-can-work-in-the-u-s</guid><description> Foreign doctors, nurses, and healthcare professionals can work in the U.S. through visa sponsorship, credential verification, and state licensing. Capitol Law Partners offers legal guidance throughout this process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Form I-485? How to Complete? Step-by-Step </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/whatis-form-i-485-howtocomplete-step-by-step</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/whatis-form-i-485-howtocomplete-step-by-step</guid><description>This guide explains how to accurately complete Form I-485 using clear, practical steps adapted from real applicant experiences. It highlights the strict requirement to enter information exactly as shown on your passport, use only English letters, and disclose any additional citizenships or prior immigration filings. </description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ways to Get a Green Card in the United States </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/ways-to-get-a-green-card-in-the-united-states</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/ways-to-get-a-green-card-in-the-united-states</guid><description> There are multiple ways to get a Green Card: family sponsorship (parents, siblings, fiancé(e)/spouse), employment-based visas (EB categories), the Diversity Visa Lottery, and other special programs. Capitol Law Partners helps clients choose the best path and provides legal support to achieve permanent residency. </description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intellectual Property Law in the U.S</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/intellectual-property-law-in-the-u-s</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/intellectual-property-law-in-the-u-s</guid><description>This article provides a practical overview of Intellectual Property (IP) law in the United States, explaining how patents, trademarks, copyrights, and trade secrets safeguard innovation. It also highlights current debates around artificial intelligence and intellectual property, offering guidance for businesses and creators seeking legal protection. </description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Fill Out the DS-160 Form - A Step by Step </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/howtofillouttheds-160-form-a-step-by-step</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/howtofillouttheds-160-form-a-step-by-step</guid><description>The DS-160 Form, which is mandatory for US visa applications, is a detailed electronic visa form that is filled out online. It is very important that the form is completed accurately and in full for the application to proceed smoothly. Here are the key points you need to know when filling out the form..</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 09:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Can I Bring My Family to the usa? | Immigration Process</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/bringing-your-family-to-the-us-immigration-process</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/bringing-your-family-to-the-us-immigration-process</guid><description>The most critical elements in the US immigration process are preparing the correct forms, providing complete information, and starting the process on time. Correct Forms provides professional support to its clients in these three key areas, ensuring that applications proceed without error. By minimizing the long waiting times caused by incomplete or incorrect documents, they make their clients&apos; journey to build a new life in America reliable, fast, and stress-free.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Purchasing a Home Without Citizenship </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/purchasing-a-home-without-citizenship</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/purchasing-a-home-without-citizenship</guid><description>Buying property in the United States is fully accessible to non-citizens. With the right team of experts and careful financial planning, you can successfully purchase real estate for both personal use and investment purposes. </description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Establish a Sole Proprietorship? Step by Step</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/howtoestablisha-soleproprietorship-step-by-step</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/howtoestablisha-soleproprietorship-step-by-step</guid><description>In this article, you will find the basic steps for setting up a company in the USA and the points to consider in a simple and understandable way. .</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immigration Legal Support | Washington | New York | Virginia </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-legal-support-washington-new-york-virginia</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-legal-support-washington-new-york-virginia</guid><description>Capitol Law Partners — Immigration Legal Support in Washington, New York, and Virginia..</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Visa Application Was Denied What Should I Do? </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/my-visa-applicationwasdeniedwhatshouldi-do</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/my-visa-applicationwasdeniedwhatshouldi-do</guid><description>Getting a U.S. visa denial doesn’t have to be the end of your immigration journey. Learn what steps to take after your application is refused and how the experienced attorneys at Capitol Law Partners in Washington, D.C. and Chicago can guide you through reapplication or appeal for a stronger case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is Form I-130? 2025 Update</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/whatis-form-i-130-2025-update</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/whatis-form-i-130-2025-update</guid><description>USCIS has released updated October 2025 I-130 processing times. Find out how long approvals take, what’s causing delays, and where the backlog stands</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Makes a Will Valid in Texas? What are the Requirements?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-makes-a-will-valid-in-texas-what-are-the-requirements</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-makes-a-will-valid-in-texas-what-are-the-requirements</guid><description>In this article, our estate planning attorneys at Capitol Law Partners explain exactly what makes a Will valid in Texas, whether it needs to be notarized, and why working with a professional lawyer helps ensure your estate plan stands the test of time.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chamber of Commerce Sues Over Trump’s New $100,000 H-1B Visa Fee</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/chamber-of-commerce-sues-over-trumps-new-100-000-h-1b-visa-fee-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/chamber-of-commerce-sues-over-trumps-new-100-000-h-1b-visa-fee-2</guid><description>The U.S. Chamber of Commerce filed a federal lawsuit on October 16, 2025, arguing that the Trump administration’s $100,000 H-1B visa fee is “unlawful and economically damaging.” The Chamber says the fee exceeds the limits allowed under the Immigration and Nationality Act (INA) and would severely restrict U.S. companies’ access to skilled foreign talent — especially in tech and engineering. The case, Chamber of Commerce v. DHS (No. 25-cv-3675), is currently before the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immigrant Visa Process - A Step by Step </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/u-s-visas-immigrant-visa-process-a-step-by-step-guide</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/u-s-visas-immigrant-visa-process-a-step-by-step-guide</guid><description>This guide provides a step-by-step overview of the U.S. immigrant visa process—from submitting your initial petition to preparing for the final interview. It explains how to navigate key stages such as paying required fees, submitting Form I-864, completing the DS-260, and gathering the necessary civil and financial documents. You’ll also learn how to upload your materials correctly, monitor your case progress through CEAC, and prepare for your embassy interview. Whether you&apos;re just beginning or nearing the end of your journey, this guide helps ensure you stay informed, organized, and ready for every stage of the process. </description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Business Intellectual Property Protection Types in US</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/small-business-intellectual-property-protection-types</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/small-business-intellectual-property-protection-types</guid><description>This guide provides small business owners with a comprehensive overview of intellectual property protection, focusing on how trademarks, copyrights, patents, and trade secrets safeguard brand value and competitiveness. It explains why federal trademark registration with the USPTO is essential, outlines the step-by-step application process, and highlights the legal advantages of professional IP counsel. </description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Intellectual Property? | Copyrights | Trademarks | Patents</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/whatisintellectualproperty-copyrights-trademarks-patents</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/whatisintellectualproperty-copyrights-trademarks-patents</guid><description>This article comprehensively addresses the importance of intellectual property for businesses and the methods for protecting it. It explains the four main types of intellectual property: copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, and patents, detailing the definition, protection period, and registration process for each. The article emphasizes the impact of intellectual property rights on business value, highlighting the critical role of proper registration and legal protection in brand security and competitive advantage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding the B-1/B-2 Visitor Visa</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-b-1-b-2-visitor-visa</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-b-1-b-2-visitor-visa</guid><description>The B-1/B-2 visa allows short-term business and tourism visits to the U.S. Capitol Law Partners helps applicants prepare strong cases, avoid mistakes, and secure smooth entry for their travel needs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get a Green Card ?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/howtogetagreencard</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/howtogetagreencard</guid><description>This text explains the process of obtaining a Green Card through employment. First, you need to find a job offer from an American company. The process then consists of three stages: the PERM application, the I-140 application, and the I-485 application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US H-1B Visa Overhaul | H-1B Visa Changes - FAQ</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/us-h-1b-visa-overhaul-h-1b-visa-changes-faq</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/us-h-1b-visa-overhaul-h-1b-visa-changes-faq</guid><description>The new executive order concerning H-1B visas has introduced a mandatory $100,000 payment, but its scope and implementation remain unclear and inconsistent across agencies. </description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fastest Ways to Get a Green Card in the U.S. </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/the-fastest-ways-to-get-a-green-card-in-the-u-s</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/the-fastest-ways-to-get-a-green-card-in-the-u-s</guid><description>There are several ways to obtain a Green Card in the US, but not all options are equally fast or applicable to everyone. We are reviewing the methods with you for a fast and effective process. It is very important to consult an immigration lawyer to determine the most suitable strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the Easiest Way That Someone Can Immigrate To the USA?  </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-the-easiest-way-that-someone-can-immigrate-to-the-usa</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-the-easiest-way-that-someone-can-immigrate-to-the-usa</guid><description>The easiest ways to immigrate to the U.S. include family sponsorship, student visas leading to H-1B and green cards, the E-2 investor visa for entrepreneurs, and the EB-2 NIW for skilled professionals. Your best option depends on age, education, funds, and career goals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is an EB-2 Visa? Application Process and Timeline</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-an-eb-2-visa-application-process-and-timeline</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-an-eb-2-visa-application-process-and-timeline</guid><description>The EB-2 visa allows highly skilled professionals and individuals with advanced degrees to apply for U.S. permanent residency at any time of the year. While applications are accepted continuously, the process depends on labor certification (PERM), I-140 petition approval, and visa availability under the monthly Visa Bulletin. For those applying under the National Interest Waiver (NIW), the process is faster since PERM is not required.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 11:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I-589 Form &amp; U.S. Asylum Process Explained </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/removal-asylum-u-s-asylum-process-legal-advice</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/removal-asylum-u-s-asylum-process-legal-advice</guid><description>This article provides a comprehensive overview of the U.S. asylum process, focusing on the critical I-589 form, eligibility requirements, disqualifying factors, and common FAQs. It explains how applicants can file for asylum, the importance of proper documentation, processing times, and work authorization while awaiting a decision. Emphasizing the complexity of immigration procedures, the article highlights how Capitol Law Partners offers expert legal guidance, ensuring accurate preparation and professional handling of asylum and immigration cases in the United States.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J-1 Visa - Exchange Visitor Program Update – 2025 </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/j-1-visa-exchange-visitor-program-update-2025</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/j-1-visa-exchange-visitor-program-update-2025</guid><description> The J-1 visa remains a valuable tool for cultural and professional exchange. In 2025, with Turkey’s removal from the Skills List, new opportunities have opened for many applicants. However, the program still carries complex requirements, including sponsorship, strict work limitations, and potential 212(e) restrictions. With the right legal support, J-1 participants can confidently navigate extensions, waivers, and long-term immigration goals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Visa Attorney</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/student-visa-attorney</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/student-visa-attorney</guid><description>This step-by-step guide explains the U.S. student visa process, from choosing the right visa type and preparing documents to consular interviews and Green Card pathways. With insights from experienced student visa attorneys, it highlights how legal guidance minimizes errors, reduces denial risks, and secures long-term immigration opportunities. </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EB-3 Visa - What Is the EB-3 Visa? How to Apply ?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/eb-3-visa-what-is-the-eb-3-visa</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/eb-3-visa-what-is-the-eb-3-visa</guid><description> The EB-3 visa offers a pathway to U.S. permanent residency for skilled workers, professionals, and unskilled laborers with employer sponsorship. Capitol Law Partners assists both applicants and employers through labor certification, petition filings, and immigration strategy to secure Green Card approval. </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding Family-Based Immigration | Attorney </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-family-based-immigration-attorney</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-family-based-immigration-attorney</guid><description>Family-based immigration is one of the most important paths to lawful U.S. residency but is often slowed by complex legal rules, strict documentation requirements, and lengthy backlogs. Capitol Law Partners provides experienced legal guidance to help families avoid pitfalls, expedite cases, and achieve reunification with confidence. </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Immigration Update 2025: How Proposed Rules Affect F-1 Students and Scholars</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/u-s-immigration-update-2025-how-proposed-rules-affect-f-1-students-and-scholars</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/u-s-immigration-update-2025-how-proposed-rules-affect-f-1-students-and-scholars</guid><description>The Trump Administration’s proposed rule seeks to end the “duration of status” model for foreign students and exchange visitors, replacing it with fixed admission periods of up to four years. This change would require students to apply for extensions through USCIS, leading to stricter oversight and regular vetting. </description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Corporate Law?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-corporate-law</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-corporate-law</guid><description>This article explains the essentials of corporate law in the United States, including business formation, governance, M&amp;A, contracts, compliance, and disputes. It highlights why corporate law matters for businesses of all sizes and how Capitol Law Partners supports clients with tailored legal strategies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Become a Soldier in the USA </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-to-become-a-soldier-in-the-usa</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-to-become-a-soldier-in-the-usa</guid><description>This article explains the main steps and requirements for joining the U.S. Army and other military branches. It highlights eligibility rules, enlistment procedures, and the role of legal considerations for immigrants and non-citizens. Written for informational purposes by Capitol Law Partners, this guide helps readers understand the process of becoming a soldier in the United States. </description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is Crimmigration?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-crimmigration</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-crimmigration</guid><description>Crimmigration combines criminal and immigration law, creating serious consequences for non-citizens facing charges. At Capitol Law Partners, we guide clients through both systems—protecting immigration status, avoiding deportation, and securing future opportunities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the United States Immigration System Works</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-the-united-states-immigration-system-works</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-the-united-states-immigration-system-works</guid><description>This guide explains how the U.S. immigration system works, covering temporary visas, green cards, and citizenship. With insight from Capitol Law Partners, individuals and businesses gain practical strategies to navigate legal requirements, avoid pitfalls, and achieve successful outcomes in their immigration journey. </description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B1/B2 Visas in the United States: What You Can and Cannot Do </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/b1-b2-visas-in-the-united-states-what-you-can-and-cannot-do</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/b1-b2-visas-in-the-united-states-what-you-can-and-cannot-do</guid><description>The B1/B2 visa is a flexible option for short-term travel, covering both business and leisure. It is best used for attending meetings, tourism, medical visits, and short-term courses. However, it is not a work or study visa, and misuse can have long-term immigration consequences. </description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speak with an Immigration Attorney: General Support &amp; Case Assistance </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/speak-with-an-immigration-attorney-general-support-case-assistance</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/speak-with-an-immigration-attorney-general-support-case-assistance</guid><description>Capitol Law Partners offers direct immigration case assistance and general support for individuals, families, and businesses. From visa applications and green card petitions to deportation defense and naturalization, our attorneys provide personalized guidance to help clients achieve their immigration goals with confidence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immigration Law in the U.S.: What You Need to Know </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-law-in-the-u-s-what-you-need-to-know</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-law-in-the-u-s-what-you-need-to-know</guid><description>Immigration law affects individuals, families, and businesses in many ways — from family petitions to employment-based visas and citizenship applications. The system is often confusing and subject to change, which makes professional guidance essential. Capitol Law Partners provides trusted immigration representation, ensuring compliance, clarity, and strong advocacy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding the H-1B Visa Process</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-h-1b-visa-process</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-h-1b-visa-process</guid><description>An expert guide to the H-1B visa process, covering the annual timeline, lottery system, petition filing, and key preparation tips for applicants and employers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Immigration Attorneys at Capitol Law Partners</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/chicago-immigration-attorneys-at-capitol-law-partners</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/chicago-immigration-attorneys-at-capitol-law-partners</guid><description>Capitol Law Partners provides trusted immigration legal services in Chicago, offering expert guidance on visas, green cards, citizenship, and complex immigration matters. Our attorneys combine in-depth knowledge of U.S. immigration law with personalized strategies to protect your rights and achieve your goalls.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding the U.S. Green Card Process: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-u-s-green-card-process-a-step-by-step-guide</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-the-u-s-green-card-process-a-step-by-step-guide</guid><description>Obtaining a U.S. Green Card — the official proof of lawful permanent residency — is a major step toward building your life in the United States. Whether your goal is to live, work, reunite with family, or eventually become a U.S. citizen, understanding the process is essential to your success. At Capitol Law Partners, our immigration attorneys guide clients through every stage with precision and care.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immigration Lawyers with Free Consultation</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-lawyers-with-free-consultation</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-lawyers-with-free-consultation</guid><description>Choosing an immigration lawyer with a free consultation can be your first smart step toward a successful U.S. immigration journey—but only if you know what to look for. Not all “free” services offer real value. During your initial meeting, pay close attention to the attorney’s experience, fee transparency, and ability to explain your case. Avoid vague answers, pressure tactics, and unlicensed &quot;consultants.&quot; At Capitol Law Partners, we combine expert legal strategy with a transparent, client-first approach—so you get the clarity and guidance you need from day one...</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is Estate Planning in the US</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-estate-planning-in-the-us</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/what-is-estate-planning-in-the-us</guid><description>Comprehensive guide on estate planning, trusts, wills, probate, guardianship, and conservatorship in the U.S. with expert insight from Capitol Law Partners..</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intellectual Property Law</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/intellectual-property-law</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/intellectual-property-law</guid><description>This article provides a concise and actionable overview of Intellectual Property Law, outlining the core IP types and their significance in business. Ideal for legal advisors, startups, and growing enterprises seeking to protect their innovations and brand identity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Immigration</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/business-immigration</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/business-immigration</guid><description>The Business Immigration process in the U.S. allows entrepreneurs, investors, and skilled professionals to live and work legally. Learn about L-1, E-2, EB-5 visas, common mistakes, and how Capitol Law Partners can guide you every step of the way...</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Law in U.S.A</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/real-estate-law-in-u-s-a</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/real-estate-law-in-u-s-a</guid><description>At Capitol Law Partners, we go beyond legal representation. We act as strategic advisors, combining deep expertise in real estate law with practical know-how to ensure every transaction is smooth, compliant, and risk-free. Whether you’re buying a single-family home, signing a commercial lease, or managing a development project, our team offers tailored legal solutions designed to protect your interests and maximize value..</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choosing The Best Lawyer For Your Legal Case </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/choosing-the-best-lawyer-for-your-legal-case</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/choosing-the-best-lawyer-for-your-legal-case</guid><description>Choosing the right attorney isn’t just about credentials — it’s about finding a trusted advocate who understands your unique legal needs and can guide you through every step of the process. With years of experience helping individuals and businesses navigate complex legal matters, we know how crucial the right legal partner can be. This guide will help you make an informed, confident decision when selecting the best lawyer for your case. </description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding Corporate Law: A Detailed Guide - Legal Aspects of Business </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-corporate-law-a-detailed-guide-legal-aspects-of-business</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/understanding-corporate-law-a-detailed-guide-legal-aspects-of-business</guid><description>This article provides a clear and comprehensive overview of the fundamentals of corporate law, explaining the legal responsibilities and obligations businesses may encounter from formation to dissolution. It explores the differences between business entity types, the duties of board members, the protection of shareholder rights, and how companies can ensure compliance with regulatory requirements. The legal aspects of key corporate decisions—such as mergers, acquisitions, and dissolutions—are also examined in depth. Designed as a practical guide for both entrepreneurs and corporate executives, the article highlights the connection between legal compliance and sustainable business growth. It concludes with an introduction to Capitol Law Partners and the professional legal services they offer to support businesses throughout every stage of their journey. </description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Choose the Right Legal Advisor for Your Immigration Needs </title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-to-choose-the-right-legal-advisor-for-your-immigration-needs</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-to-choose-the-right-legal-advisor-for-your-immigration-needs</guid><description>This article guides individuals in choosing the right legal advisor for complex matters like immigration. It highlights five key factors: the lawyer’s experience and expertise, valid licenses and Bar registration, clear communication, a detailed service agreement, and adherence to ethical standards. The article concludes by recommending Capitol Law Partners, emphasizing their professional and ethical legal support in guiding clients through immigration processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Do I Apply for a Visa to Come to the UK?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-do-i-apply-for-a-visa-to-come-to-the-uk</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-do-i-apply-for-a-visa-to-come-to-the-uk</guid><description>If you are planning to travel to the United Kingdom, you need to determine in advance the type of visa you need to apply for, depending on the purpose of your trip and your citizenship status. This guide clearly and simply explains which visas you can apply for as a visitor, student, worker, or family member, the application requirements, and important points to consider...</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Businnes Litigation</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/businnes-litigation</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/businnes-litigation</guid><description>This article provides a comprehensive overview of business litigation, including what it entails, why it matters for business owners, and the most common types of legal disputes companies face—such as breach of contract, partnership disagreements, and employment-related claims. It also outlines key strategies to minimize litigation risk and explains when to consult a commercial litigation attorney. ..</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Path to US Citizenship: Requirements for EU Citizenship</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/path-to-us-citizenship-requirements-for-eu-citizenship</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/path-to-us-citizenship-requirements-for-eu-citizenship</guid><description>Path to US Citizenship: Requirements for EU Citizenship. How to Become an EU Citizen? What are the Necessary Requirements?..</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Can You Get Legal Advice for Your Case?</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/how-can-you-get-legal-advice-for-your-case</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/how-can-you-get-legal-advice-for-your-case</guid><description>Need legal advice? Not sure where to start? Choose a law firm that specializes in your case. Expertise matters. Trusted legal guidance. Personalized strategy. Quick contact via our website. Reach out today and protect your rights..</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Visa</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/investment-visa</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/investment-visa</guid><description>The EB-5 and E-2 visas are two key U.S. immigration options for foreign investors. The EB-5 visa offers a direct path to a Green Card through a high-capital investment ($800,000–$1.05 million) that creates at least 10 U.S. jobs. In contrast, the E-2 visa is a faster, lower-cost option for nationals of treaty countries who want to start and run a business in the U.S., though it doesn’t lead directly to permanent residency. Choosing between them depends on your goals, investment capacity, and nationality...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>⁠Immigration Mandamus Lawsuits</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-mandamus-lawsuits</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/immigration-mandamus-lawsuits</guid><description>Learn about the process of immigration mandamus cases...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Removal Proceedings</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/removal-proceedings</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/removal-proceedings</guid><description>Removal Proceedings</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Affirmative Asylum</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/affirmative-asylum</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/affirmative-asylum</guid><description>Affirmative Asylum</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking the EB-2 NIW: How to Qualify for a National Interest Waiver</title><link>https://capitollawpartners.com/dummy</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://capitollawpartners.com/dummy</guid><description>Learn how to navigate the EB-2 National Interest Waiver process, including eligibility criteria and application steps for permanent residency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>